Phạm Phái Hà

Front-end developer

0886323318

Ha Noi

MY WEBSITE

https://www.phamha.info/

OBJECTIVE

I'm currently a developer. I'm a front-end developer with over 4 years of experience. I has worked in the fields of software development, E-commerce, ERP, CRM and blockchain related projects. I is passionate about technology and cryptocurrency.

EDUCATION

August - 2017 - 2021

MAJOR:INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Transportation Technology University

4th year student

August - 2018 - 2021

MAJOR: WEB FULL-STACK

VTC Academy

Graduated

SKILL

Devops:

Azure could service. github action, CICD, S3

Framework:

Reactjs, Nextjs, Vuejs, Angular (typescript)

Blockchain:

hardhat, ertherjs, web3js, metamask, sodility

UI:

Material ui, Antd, Bootstrap, Tailwild css, Storybook, SCSS

Oath2:

google, Microsoft, facebook

Manage:

Google Analytics

Base soure:

webpack, eslint, commint lint, babel

Realtime:

mqtt, firebase, socket

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tekmate Software Solution

12-2019 - 04-2020

PROJECTNAME :XAYDUNG CO

Member: 9 (1 Tester, 6 Dev, 1 PM, 1 BA)

Position: Intern

Project Description: Building web app for selling construction company's tools like Fiver.

Technology: React JS

Work Description: create UI/UX, work with BE dev and add api

GMO-Z.com Runsystem

07-2020 - 12-2020

PROJECTNAME: SALE FIE

Member: 12 (1 Tester, 8 Dev, 1 PM, 1 BA, 1 QA)

Position: ReactJs developer

Project Description: staffs management project, Technology Award 'Sao Khue 2021' of

vietnam.

Award Link: https://runsystem.net/vi/2021/04/26/gmo-z-com-runsystem-nhan-cu-dup-2-

danh-hieu-sao-khue-2021-cho-san-pham-chuyen-doi/

Technology: React JS

Work Description: make UI/UX like a design, work with BE dev and add api

Link: https://salefie.vn/

GMO-Z.com Runsystem

12-2020 - 05-2021

PROJECTNAME: KAIKE

Member: 11 (1 Tester, 7 Dev, 1 PM, 1 BA, 1 QA)

Position: ReactJs developer

Project Description: website accounting project. Helping users who do not know about

accounting can also do a professional accountant

Technology: React JS (webpack)

Work Description: make UI/UX like a design, work with BE dev and add api

Link: https://app.kaike.vn/

GMO-Z.com Runsystem

05-2021 - 07-2021

PROJECTNAME: ADMIN PL

Member: 13 (3 Tester, 7 Dev, 1 PM, 1 BA, 1 OA)

Position: ReactJs developer

Project Description :work time management

Technology: React JS (webpack)

Work Description: make UI/UX like a design, work with BE dev and add api, manage project

front-end Link: private

GMO-Z.com Runsystem

07-2021 - 09-2021

PROJECTNAME: MYSGR (ONSITE)

Member: 9 (1 Tester, 7 Dev, 1 PM)

Position: ReactJs developer, review code, tech lead Project Description: Staffs management off Sun Group

Technology: React JS (webpack), Node (ODDO)

Work Description: make UI/UX like a design, work with BE dev and add api, manage project

front-end, work with filebase, backend ODDO, review code, merge code

Link: private

Filink

11-2021 - 3-2022

PROJECTNAME: LSTN (PRODUCT)

Member: (5 front-end)

Position: ReactJs developer, teamlead

Project Description : Auction of NFT products

Technology: React JS ,Web3js

Work Description: make UI/UX like a design, work with BE dev and add api, manage project front-end, call data from Blockchain. convert many money, connect metamask wallet

Link: https://listencampaign.com/listen_campaign_elements

FPT

3-2022 - 5-2023

PROJECTNAME: AURA-SAFE(PRODUCT)

Member: (1 front-end)

Position: ReactJs developer,

Project Description: Look like gnosis safe, manager many wallet cryto

Technology: React JS ,Web3js

Work Description: make UI/UX like a design, work with BE dev and add api,call data form

Blockchain. connect keplr, coin 98 wallet

Link: https://app.pyxis.aura.network/welcome

PROJECTNAME: GG LIVE (FREELANCER)

Member: (3 front-end)

Box Studio

5-2023 - 7-2023

Position: ReactJs developer,

Project Description : Web livestream

Work Description: make UI/UX like a design, work with BE

Technology: Nextjs

Link: https://gglive.vn/ © topcv.vn